<resources>

    <!--Written by Kanayo-->
    <!--User Visible Titles-->
    <string name="app_name">RRsCasino</string>
    <string name="helpTitle">Help Menu</string>
    <string name="helpDescription">What would you like to know about?</string>
    <string name="topics">Topics</string>
    <string name="pokerHelpDescription">Learn the basics of our Poker App</string>
    <string name="bjackHelpDescription">Learn the basics of our Blackjack App</string>
    <string name="Overview">UI Overview</string>
    <string name="HowToWin">How To Win</string>
    <string name="Actions">Actions</string>


    <!--Interior XML Used Titles-->
    <string name="pokerImgButtonDesc">pokerButton</string>
    <string name="bjackImgButtonDesc">bjackButton</string>

    <!--Dialog Text-->
    <string name="bjOverviewDescription">
        To start playing Blackjack, navigate to the main menu, click play, then the
        Blackjack icon. The layout simulates a casino table.
            The cards at the top of the screen are the <b>dealer\'s hand</b>. The cards
            on the bottom is <b>your hand</b>.
            Above each player\'s hands are their current hand\'s <b>score.</b>
            Below the hands there are your <b>action buttons.</b>
        At the bottom is the <b>betting slider</b> and current <b>balance.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="bjActionsDescription">Blackjack allows for 6 different actions.
            <b>Deal</b> will start the game. It will deal two cards to both players.
                One card will be face-up from the dealer\'s hand and both your cards will be
                visible to you.
            <b>Double</b> will double your current bet. It is a double edged sword, almost literally.
                This button is only available when you have 11 or less in your hand.
            <b>Hit</b> informs the dealer to deal one more card to you. Be careful, only <b>Hit</b>
                when safe.
            <b>Stay</b> ends your turn and allows the dealer to deal cards to self-deal.
            <b>Split</b> when you have two of the same value cards in your hand you\'re able to
        <b>split</b>
                your hand in two.
    </string>

    <string name="bjWinningDescription">
        The goal of the game is to achieve a hand score of 21, or at least a score better than the
        dealer. All <b>numerical cards</b> values are equal to their actual worth in-game.
        All <b>face cards</b> are worth 10. The odd card out is the <b>Ace</b>, it has a value of
        both 1 and 11. It\'s value is automatically adjusted during the game. That means if you have
        two face cards in hand and pull an ace, you would have a score of 21, not 31.
        <b>Blackjack</b> is ultimately a game of chance but with a bit of luck on your side
        victories will be normal place.
    </string>
    <string name="pOverviewDescription">
        Clicking on the poker app shows the main poker screen.
    </string>
    <string name="pActionsDescription">

    </string>
    <string name="pWinningDescription">

    </string>
</resources>